Indiana University President's Office Correspondence, 1913-1937 C286
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1913-1937 (Box 1)
  - De (Box 75)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 75)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 75)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 75)
    - 1935 (Box 75)
    - 1936 (Box 75)
    - 1937 (Box 75)
  - Degner, Dorrit, 1917 (Box 75)
  - Degner, Evelyn, 1917 (Box 75)
  - Degner, Lorena, 1914-1923 (Box 75)
  - Dei-Dek, 1913-1923 (Box 75)
  - Del (Box 75)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 75)
    - 1925-1930 (Box 75)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 75)
  - Delgado, Francisco A., 1925-1935 (Box 75)
  - Delta Chi, 1916-1936 (Box 75)
  - Dem (Box 75)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 75)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 75)
    - 1928-1937 (Box 75)
  - Den (Box 76)
    - 1914 (Box 76)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 76)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 76)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 76)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 76)
  - Den-Deq (Box 76)
    - 1915-1920 (Box 76)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 76)
  - Denver File Clay Company, 1914 (Box 76)
  - Dental School, 1924-1928 (Box 76)
  - Dentistry School (Box 76)
    - 1926-1932 (Box 76)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 76)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 76)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 76)
  - Dep, 1923-1931 (Box 76)
  - Deputy, Manfred W., 1915-1930 (Box 76)
  - Depauw University (Box 76)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 76)
    - 1920-1924 (Box 76)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 76)
    - 1928 (Box 77)
    - 1929 (Box 77)
    - 1930 (Box 77)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 77)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 77)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 77)
  - Der, 1923-1937 (Box 77)
  - Dev, 1923-1937 (Box 77)
  - Der-Dev, 1913-1923 (Box 77)
  - Dew-Dez, 1913-1923 (Box 77)
  - Dh, 1919-1923 (Box 77)
  - Dia-Dic, 1913-1923 (Box 77)
  - Di, 1923-1925 (Box 77)
  - Di (Box 77)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 77)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 77)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 77)
  - Di (Box 77)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 77)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 77)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 77)
  - Dia-Dic, 1913-1923 (Box 78)
  - Did-Dik, 1913-1923 (Box 78)
  - Die, 1923-1937 (Box 78)
  - Diggs, Elder Watson, 1916-1927 (Box 78)
  - Dil-Dim, 1913-1923 (Box 78)
  - Dil (Box 78)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 78)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 78)
  - Dill, Elizabeth and Dwight—correspondence, 1917-1918 (Box 78)
  - Din-Dis, 1913-1919 (Box 78)
  - Dit-Diz, 1913-1923 (Box 78)
  - Doa-Doc, 1913-1923 (Box 78)
  - Do (Box 78)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 78)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 78)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 78)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 78)
  - Dod-Dok, 1913-1923 (Box 78)
  - Doh, 1923-1937 (Box 78)
  - Dol-Doz (Box 78)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 78)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 78)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 78)
  - Dol-Doz (Box 79)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 79)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 79)
  - Donn (Box 79)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 79)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 79)
  - Dor (Box 79)
    - 1923-1931 (Box 79)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 79)
  - Dou (Box 79)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 79)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 79)
  - Dow (Box 79)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 79)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 79)
  - Dr (Box 79)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 79)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 79)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 79)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 79)
  - Dra, 1914-1923 (Box 79)
  - Dre, 1914-1923 (Box 79)
  - Drinking (alcohol) (Box 79)
  - Driver, Lee L. (Box 80)
  - Dri-Dry, 1914-1923 (Box 80)
  - Dri, 1923-1937 (Box 80)
  - Dua-Duf, 1913-1923 (Box 80)
  - Dug-Dum, 1914-1923 (Box 80)
  - Du (Box 80)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 80)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 80)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 80)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 80)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 80)
  - Dun (Box 80)
    - 1914-1920 (Box 80)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 80)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 80)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 80)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 80)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 80)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 80)
  - Dunham, Mary, 1917 (Box 80)
  - Duniway, C.A., 1914-1917 (Box 80)
  - Duo-Dur, 1914-1923 (Box 80)
  - Duplication of Courses—miscellaneous, undated (Box 80)
    - (Folder 1) (Box 80)
    - (Folder 2) (Box 81)
  - Dur, 1923-1937 (Box 81)
  - Dus-Duz, 1914-1923 (Box 81)
  - Dw-Dy (Box 81)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 81)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 81)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 81)
  - E (Box 81)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 81)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 81)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 81)
    - 1929 (Box 81)
    - 1930 (Box 81)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 81)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 81)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 81)
  - Ea-Eb (Box 81)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 81)
    - 1918-1921 (Box 81)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 81)
  - Earlham College (Box 81)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 81)
    - 1924-1930 (Box 82)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 82)
  - Eastern Illinois State Normal School, 1916-1917 (Box 82)
  - Eb (Box 82)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 82)
    - 1930-1936 (Box 82)
  - Ec (Box 82)
    - 1913-1926 (Box 82)
    - 1927-1933 (Box 82)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 82)
  - Ed (Box 82)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 82)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 82)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 82)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 82)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 82)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 82)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 82)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 82)
  - Ed (Box 83)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 83)
  - Edie, Professor L.D., 1925-1927 (Box 83)
  - Edison Scholarship (Box 83)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 83)
    - 1930 (Box 83)
  - Edler, John, 1914-1917 (Box 83)
  - Edm, 1923-1937 (Box 83)
  - Edmondson, Clarence E. (Box 83)
    - Re: Committee on Student Health (Box 83)
      - 1913 (Box 83)
      - 1914 (Box 83)
      - 1915 (Box 83)
    - 1920-1928 (Box 83)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 83)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 83)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 83)
  - Edmondson, Edna Hatfield, 1920-1924 (Box 83)
  - Edmondson, Frank Kelley, 1929-1937 (Box 83)
  - Education, School of (Box 83)
    - The Junior College 1927 (Box 83)
    - Need Report, 1925 (Box 83)
  - Education, U.S. Department (proposed), 1925 (Box 83)
  - Educational Conference and Centennial, undated (Box 294)
  - Educational Conference—correspondence about delegates to, 1920 (Box 83)
    - (A-L) (Box 83)
    - (M-Z) (Box 83)
  - Educational drive for state institutions, 1920 (Box 83)
  - Ee-Ek (Box 83)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 83)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 83)
  - Eg, 1923-1937 (Box 83)
  - Ei (Box 83)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 83)
  - Ei (Box 84)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 84)
  - Eigenmann, Dean Carl H. (Box 84)
    - 1913-1915 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 84)
    - January-June 1916 (Box 84)
    - July-August 1916 (Box 84)
    - September-December 1916 (Box 84)
    - 1917 (Box 84)
    - January-May 1918 (Box 84)
    - June-December 1918 (Box 84)
    - 1919 (Box 84)
    - January-August 1920 (Box 84)
    - September 1920-May 1921 (Box 84)
    - June-December 1921 (Box 84)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 84)
    - 1924-1927 (Box 84)
  - Eimer and Amend, 1913-1918 (Box 84)
  - Ela-Elk, 1913-1923 (Box 84)
  - El (Box 84)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 84)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 84)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 84)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 84)
  - Electric Appliance Company, 1913-1921 (Box 84)
  - Electrosurgical Instrument Company, 1913-1914 (Box 84a)
  - Eliot, Charles W.—memorial meeting, 1927; (2 folders) (Box 84a)
  - Ell (Box 85)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 85)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 85)
    - 1922-1925 (Box 85)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 85)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 85)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 85)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 85)
  - Elliott, Frank R.—publicity department (Box 85)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 85)
    - 1924 (Box 85)
    - 1925 (Box 85)
    - 1926 (Box 85)
    - 1927 (Box 85)
    - 1928 (Box 85)
    - 1929 (Box 85)
    - 1930 (Box 85)
    - 1931 (Box 85)
  - Elliott, Frank R.—publicity department (Box 86)
    - January-May, 1932 (Box 86)
    - June-December, 1932 (Box 86)
    - 1933 (Box 86)
    - 1934 (Box 86)
    - 1935 (Box 86)
    - 1936 (Box 86)
    - 1937 (Box 86)
  - Elliott, Robert C., 1923-1924 (Box 86)
  - Elm-Els, 1913-1923 (Box 86)
  - Elt-Elz, 1913-1923 (Box 86)
  - Em (Box 86)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 86)
    - 1925-1930 (Box 86)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 86)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 86)
  - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars, 1933-1934 (Box 86)
  - Emerson, Dean Charles P. (Box 86)
    - 1914 (Box 86)
    - 1915 (Box 86)
    - 1916 (Box 86)
    - 1917 (Box 86)
    - 1918 (Box 87)
    - 1919 (Box 87)
    - 1920 (Box 87)
    - 1921 (Box 87)
    - 1922 (Box 87)
    - 1923 (Box 87)
    - 1924 (Box 87)
    - 1925 (Box 87)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 87)
    - 1927 (Box 87)
    - January-June, 1928 (Box 87)
    - July-December, 1928 (Box 87)
    - January-May, 1929 (Box 87)
    - June-December, 1929 (Box 87)
    - January-June, 1930 (Box 87)
    - July-December, 1930 (Box 87)
    - January-May, 1931 (Box 87)
    - June-December, 1931, 1932 (Box 87)
  - Empire Stone Company (Clear Creek, Indiana), 1930 (Box 87)
  - En (Box 87)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 87)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 87)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 87)
    - September 1928-1932 (Box 87)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 87)
  - Ena-Eng, 1914-1923 (Box 87)
  - Endowment Fund, undated (Box 87)
  - Endowment Fund Drive—Frank J. Lindley correspondence, 1925 (Box 87)
  - Engl (Box 87)
    - 1923-1932 (Box 87)
  - Engl (Box 88)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 88)
  - English Department, 1914-1917 (Box 88)
  - English position applications, 1919-1921 (Box 88)
  - Enh-Enz, 1914-1923 (Box 88)
  - Enrollment in classes (Box 88)
    - Answers to Dr. Bryan's letter to department heads, 1924-1925 (Box 88)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 88)
  - Entrance requirements—answers to questionnaire concerning national bodies which fix entrance requirements, 1924-1925 (Box 88)
  - Eo-Eq, 1914-1923 (Box 88)
  - Equipment for new buildings, 1936-1937 (Box 88)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Company (group insurance) (Box 88)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 88)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 88)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 88)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 88)
  - Er (Box 88)
    - 1913-1929 (Box 88)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 88)
  - Es (Box 88)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 88)
    - 1921-1929 (Box 88)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 88)
  - Esarey, Logan (Box 88)
    - 1913-1925 (Box 88)
    - 1926-1933 (Box 88)
  - Estonia—letter from regarding physical education, 1931 (Box 88)
  - Et-Eu, 1913-1923 (Box 88)
  - Et, 1923-1929 (Box 88)
  - Eugenics, Internation Commission on, 1922 (Box 88)
  - Eugenics, International Congress on, 1914, 1932 (Box 88)
  - Ev (Box 88)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 88)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 88)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 88)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 88)
  - Eva, 1913-1923 (Box 89)
  - Evans, Louis E. (122 East Michigan Street, Indianapolis), 1936-1937 (Box 89)
  - Evansville College (Box 89)
    - 1922-1927 (Box 89)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 89)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 89)
  - Eve-Evy, 1913-1923 (Box 89)
  - Ew-Ez, 1913-1914 (school year) (Box 89)
  - Ew (Box 89)
    - September 1914-1927 (Box 89)
    - 1928-1937 (Box 89)
  - Ewbank, Judge Louis B., 1924 (Box 89)
  - Ex-Ez September, 1914-1923 (Box 89)
  - Exchange scholarships for students, 1937 (Box 89)
  - Exchange scholarships for foreign students, 1937-1942 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee, 1918-1928 (Box 89)
  - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees, 1928-1937 (Box 89)
  - Extension Division (Box 89)
    - undated (Box 89)
    - Annual report, 1919-1920 (Box 89)
    - Bloomington (Box 89)
      - 1920-1921 (Box 89)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 89)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 89)
      - 1926 (Box 89)
      - 1927 (Box 89)
      - 1928 (Box 90)
      - 1929 (Box 90)
      - 1930 (Box 90)
      - 1931-1932 (Box 90)
  - Extension Division (Box 90)
    - Bloomington (Box 90)
      - 1933-1934 (Box 90)
      - 1935 (Box 90)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 90)
    - CCC Camps (Box 90)
      - 1934-1935 (Box 90)
    - CWA Information (Box 90)
      - 1933-1934 (Box 90)
    - East Chicago, Hammond, and Whiting Center, 1931-1937 (Box 90)
    - Fort Wayne (Box 90)
      - 1921-1922, 1927-1930 (Box 90)
      - 1931-1937 (Box 90)
    - Gary, 1927-1937 (Box 90)
    - Group Study Information, 1933-1934 (Box 90)
    - Indianapolis (Box 90)
      - 1920-1922 (Box 90)
      - 1922-1925 (Box 90)
      - 1926-1927 (Box 90)
    - Indianapolis Center (Box 90)
      - 1928 (Box 90)
      - 1929 (Box 90)
      - 1930 (Box 90)
      - 1931 (Box 91)
      - 1932-1933 (Box 91)
      - 1934-1937 (Box 91)
    - South Bend and Mishawaka Center (228 S. St. Joseph St., South Bend) (Box 91)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 91)
    - Traveling Theatre, 1935 (Box 91)
    - WPA, 1935-1936 (Box 91)
    - Suggested texts for WPA Groups, 1935-1936 (Box 91)
  - Extra sections, 1937 (Box 91)
  - F (Box 91)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 91)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 91)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 91)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 91)
  - Faa-Fak (Box 91)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 91)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 91)
  - F&N Lawn Mower Company, 1916-1920 (Box 91)
  - Faculty (Box 91)
    - 1913-1921 (Box 91)
    - 1922-1924 (Box 91)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 91)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 91)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 91)
  - Faculty Club, 1914-1921 (Box 91)
  - Faculty announcements, 1931 (Box 91)
  - Faculty matters, 1935-1967; 2 Folders (Box 294)
  - Faculty memo, September 11, 1916 (Box 91)
  - Faculty positions—applications (Box 91)
    - 1931 (Box 91)
  - Faculty positions—applications (Box 92)
  - January-March, 1932 (Box 92)
    - April-June 1932 (Box 92)
    - July-December 1932 (Box 92)
    - January-April 1933 (Box 92)
    - May-December 1933 (Box 92)
    - January-May 1934 (Box 92)
    - June 1934-April 1935 (Box 92)
    - May-December 1935 (Box 92)
    - January-April 1936 (Box 92)
    - May-December 1936 (Box 92)
    - January-March 1937 (Box 92)
    - April-December 1937 (Box 92)
  - Faculty salaries—IU, undated; (2 folders) (Box 92)
  - Fal-Faq, 1913-1923 (Box 92)
  - Fal, 1923-1937 (Box 92)
  - Far (Box 92)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 92)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 92)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 92)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 92)
  - Farmer's Guide, after, 1925? (Box 92)
  - Fas, 1924-1937? (Box 92)
  - Fas-Faz, 1913-1923 (Box 93)
  - Fea-Fek, 1913-1923 (Box 93)
  - Fe (Box 93)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 93)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 93)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 93)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 93)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 93)
  - Federal Board for Vocational Education (Box 93)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 93)
    - January-June, 1922 (Box 93)
    - July-December, 1922 (Box 93)
    - 1923 (Box 93)
  - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (F.D.I.C.), 1935-1936 (Box 93)
  - Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works, Washington, D.C. (Box 93)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 93)
    - 1935 (Box 93)
  - Federal Emergency Relief Administration (FERA) (Box 93)
    - 1934 (Box 93)
    - 1935 (Box 93)
  - Fedler, Clara—acting head, 1926-1928 (Box 94)
  - Fees (Box 94)
    - Non-resident fee schedule, proposals to change, 1936-1937 (Box 94)
    - Comparative fee schedule, 1936-1937 (Box 94)
  - Fel-Feq, 1914-1923 (Box 94)
  - Fel (Box 94)
    - 1923-1932 (Box 94)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 94)
  - Fellows, Mattie Mae, 1921-1928 (Box 94)
  - Feltus, Paul L. (Box 94)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 94)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 94)
  - Fen, 1913-1914 (Box 94)
  - Fer (Box 94)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 94)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 94)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 94)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 94)
  - Ferguson, Jesse D., 1917-1937 (Box 94)
  - Fertsch, Albert, post, 1913 (Box 94)
  - Fes-Fez, 1913-1923 (Box 94)
  - Fesler, James W. (Box 94)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 94)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 94)
    - 1920-September 1922 (Box 94)
    - 1923-September 1924 (Box 94)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 94)
    - 1928 (Box 94)
    - 1929 (Box 94)
    - 1930 (Box 94)
    - January-May 1931 (Box 94)
  - Fesler, James W. (Box 95)
    - June-December 1931 (Box 95)
    - January-May 1932 (Box 95)
    - June-December 1932 (Box 95)
  - Fesler, James W. (Box 95)
    - 1933 (Box 95)
    - 1934-1936 (Box 95)
    - 1934 (Box 95)
    - 1935 (Box 95)
    - 1936 (Box 95)
    - Board Letters (Box 95)
      - 1919-1920 (Box 95)
      - 1920-1922 (Box 95)
      - 1922-1923, (2 folders) (Box 95)
      - 1923-1924, 1925-1930 (Box 95)
      - 1924-1925, (2 folders) (Box 95)
      - 1931-1932, 1933-1936 (Box 95)
      - 1932-1933 (Box 95)
  - Feuillerat, Professor M. Albert, 1923-1924 (Box 95)
  - Fia-Fik, 1913-1923? (Box 95)
  - Fi (Box 96)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 96)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 96)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 96)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 96)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 96)
  - Fidelity and Casualty Company of New York, 1936-1937 (Box 96)
  - Field House, 1927-1930 (Box 96)
  - Field, Marshall and Company, 1913-1922 (Box 96)
  - Files, transfer list of, 1916-1917 (Box 96)
  - Fil-Fim, 1913-1923 (Box 96)
  - Fin-Fir, 1913-1923 (Box 96)
  - Fin (Box 96)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 96)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 96)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 96)
  - Finance Meeting—minutes, 1929 (Box 96)
  - Financial Report, 1920 (Box 96)
  - Finley, Georgia E., 1914-1937 (Box 96)
  - Finn, 1923-1937 (Box 96)
  - Fire Marshall—report on Robert Long Hospital, 1918 (Box 96)
  - Fireproof Film Company, 1914 (Box 96)
  - Firestone Tire & Rubber Company, 1937 (Box 96)
  - First National Bank of Bloomington (Box 96)
    - 1914-1925 (Box 96)
  - First National Bank of Bloomington (Box 97)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 97)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 97)
  - Fis (Box 97)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 97)
    - 1920-1924 (Box 97)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 97)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 97)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 97)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 97)
  - Fish, William S., 1929 (Box 97)
  - Fisher, L.L., 1927-1933 (Box 97)
  - Fit-Fiz, 1913-1923 (Box 97)
  - Fit, 1923-1937 (Box 97)
  - Fitzgerald, 1913-1923 (Box 97)
  - Fitzpatrick, 1913-1923 (Box 97)
  - Fitzsimmons, L.C., 1928-1934 (Box 97)
  - Fl (Box 97)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 97)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 97)
  - Fla-Fle, 1913-1923 (Box 97)
  - Fle (Box 98)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 98)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 98)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 98)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 98)
  - Fleming, 1914-1923 (Box 98)
  - Fletcher, 1913-1923 (Box 98)
  - Fletcher American National Bank, 1934-1935 (Box 98)
  - Fletcher Savings & Trust Co. (Box 98)
    - 1918-1924 (Box 98)
    - 1925-1930 (Box 98)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 98)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 98)
  - Fletcher Trust Company, 1935-1937 (Box 98)
  - Fli-Flo, 1913-1920s (Box 98)
  - Florida, University of, 1915-1917 (Box 98)
  - Flour City Ornamental Iron Company, 1921-1922 (Box 98)
  - Flo (Box 98)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 98)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 98)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 98)
  - Flo (Box 99)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 99)
  - Fly, 1914-1923 (Box 99)
  - Foa-Fok, 1914-1923 (Box 99)
  - Fo (Box 99)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 99)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 99)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 99)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 99)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 99)
  - Fol, 1913-1923 (Box 99)
  - Foley, A.L. (Box 99)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 99)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 99)
    - 1924-1929 (Box 99)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 99)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 99)
  - Foley, John P., 1914-1918 (Box 99)
  - Folklore, undated (Box 99)
  - Fom-Foq, 1913-1923 (Box 99)
  - Football, 1924 (Box 99)
  - Football tickets (Box 99)
    - Complimentary tickets—state officials, senators, representatives, 1937 (Box 99)
    - Correspondence re: tickets, 1933-1937 (Box 99)
  - For (Box 100)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 100)
    - 1918-1921 (Box 100)
    - 1922-1924 (Box 100)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 100)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 100)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 100)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 100)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 100)
  - Foreign students—See: Exchange Scholarships (Box 100)
  - Forg, 1923-1937 (Box 100)
  - Fort Wayne Center (Box 100)
    - Bookstore, 1927-1936 (Box 100)
    - Fee accounts, 1927-1930 (Box 100)
  - Fort Wayne Printing Company, 1916-1918 (Box 100)
  - Fos (Box 100)
    - 1913-1926 (Box 100)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 100)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 100)
  - Foster, 1913-1923 (Box 100)
  - Foster, John Watson, 1915-1922 (Box 100)
  - Fot-Fow, 1913-1923 (Box 100)
  - Fou, 1923-1937 (Box 101)
  - Fox-Foz, 1913-1923 (Box 101)
  - Fr (Box 101)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 101)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 101)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 101)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 101)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 101)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 101)
  - Fra (Box 101)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 101)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 101)
  - Franke, 1923-1931 (Box 101)
  - Frankfurt Ice and Coal Company, 1919-1920 (Box 101)
  - Franklin College (Box 101)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 101)
    - 1924-1930 (Box 101)
  - Franklin College (Box 102)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 102)
  - Franzen, Carl G.F., undated (Box 102)
  - Fraser, 1916-1923 (Box 102)
  - Fraternities (Box 102)
    - c.1931 (Box 102)
    - House Mothers, 1925 (Box 102)
  - Freeman, 1913-1923 (Box 102)
  - Fre (Box 102)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 102)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 102)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 102)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 102)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 102)
  - Freak letters, 1918-1920; 1923-1937 (Box 102)
  - Fren (Box 102)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 102)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 102)
  - French, John Wymond, 1914-1937 (Box 102)
  - Freshman-Sophomore Scrap, 1913-1914 (Box 102)
  - Fries, 1923-1937 (Box 102)
  - Fri (Box 102)
    - 1913-1926 (Box 102)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 102)
  - Fri (Box 102)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 102)
  - Fro (Box 102)
    - 1913-1937 (Box 102)
  - Fro-Fry, 1913-1923 (Box 102)
  - Fua-Fuk, 1913-1923 (Box 102)
  - Fu (Box 102)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 102)
  - Fu (Box 103)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 103)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 103)
  - Fuller, 1913-1923 (Box 103)
  - Fuller, F.E.—panoramic photographer, 1915-1917 (Box 103)
  - Ful-Fuq, 1913-1923 (Box 103)
  - Fulton Company, E.E., 1914 (Box 103)
  - Fulton Office Furniture Company, 1913-1917 (Box 103)
  - Fun (Box 103)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 103)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 103)
  - Funk & Williams, 1913-1914 (Box 103)
  - Fur-Fuz, 1913-1923 (Box 103)
  - Furniture Companies—applications to furnish furniture for new buildings, 1936 (Box 103)
  - Furniture—old—used by offices in Maxwell Hall, 1936 (Box 103)
  - Fy, 1915-1923 (Box 103)
  - G (Box 103)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 103)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 103)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 103)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 103)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 103)
  - Gaa-Gah, 1913-1923 (Box 103)
  - Gai-Gak, 1915-1923 (Box 103)
  - Gal (Box 103)
    - 1913-1924 (Box 103)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 103)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 103)
  - Gam, 1923-1937 (Box 103)
  - Gam-Gap, 1913-1923 (Box 104)
  - Gar (Box 104)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 104)
    - 1921-1924 (Box 104)
  - Gar (Box 104)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 104)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 104)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 104)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 104)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 104)
  - Garn, 1923-1937 (Box 104)
  - Garton, Joseph N., 1926-1936 (Box 104)
  - Gas-Gau, 1913; 1923 (Box 104)
  - Gas, 1923-1937 (Box 104)
  - Gatch, Willis D.—Dean of School of Medicine (Box 104)
    - 1931 (Box 104)
    - 1932 (Box 104)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 104)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 104)
  - Gav-Gaz, 1913-1923 (Box 104)
  - Gavit, Dean Bernard C. (Box 105)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 105)
    - 1935 (Box 105)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 105)
  - Gea-Geg, 1915-1923 (Box 105)
  - Geh-Gek, 1913-1923 (Box 105)
  - Ge (Box 105)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 105)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 105)
    - 1928 (Box 105)
    - 1929 (Box 105)
    - 1930 (Box 105)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 105)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 105)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 105)
  - Gel-Gep (Box 105)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 105)
  - Gel-Gep (Box 105)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 105)
  - Gel, 1923-1937 (Box 105)
  - George, Rebecca Rogers, circa 1914 (Box 105)
  - George Washington University, 1930-1937 (Box 106)
  - General Electric Company, 1919-1923 (Box 106)
  - Ger (Box 106)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 106)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 106)
    - 1927-1933 (Box 106)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 106)
  - Germann, Frank E. E., 1913-1934 (Box 106)
  - Ges, 1913-1923 (Box 106)
  - Get-Gez, 1913-1923 (Box 106)
  - Gh, 1913-1922 (Box 106)
  - Gia-Gib, 1913-1923 (Box 106)
  - Gic-Gik, 1913-1922 (Box 106)
  - Gi (Box 106)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 106)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 106)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 106)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 106)
  - Gift from Trustees, 1927; 1936 (Box 106)
  - Gil (Box 106)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 106)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 106)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 106)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 106)
  - Giles, J.T., 1913-1914 (Box 106)
  - Gill (Box 107)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 107)
    - 1929-1934 (Box 107)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 107)
  - Gim-Giz (Box 107)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 107)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 107)
  - Gimbel, Jake (Box 107)
  - Gin, 1923-1937 (Box 107)
  - Gipson, Lawrence H., 1919-1924 (Box 107)
  - Gla-Gle, 1913-1923 (Box 107)
  - Gli, 1913-1937 (Box 107)
  - Glo-Gly, 1913-1923 (Box 107)
  - Gl (Box 107)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 107)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 107)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 107)
  - Gl (Box 107)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 107)
  - Gmur, Professor M., 1919 (Box 107)
  - Goa-Gok (Box 107)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 107)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 107)
  - Go (Box 107)